[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 11]
How dare you come back?
You lost the Moon Sword.
And now you are begging me to save Liu Shao.
Tell me, why should I save her?
I want to know the truth from Master.
Back then, you asked me to escort Liu Shao
to Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
The real purpose
is that she is the only one
that can pull out the Moon Sword, right?
Yes.
You don't allow me to fall in love with her
because you know
she would die after pulling out the Moon Sword.
What else do you know?
Rumour has it that
the Moon Sword is the weapon of God of the Moonlight.
During the Battle of Two Gods,
God of the Sun sealed the Moon Sword in the mortal world.
But Liu Shao can break the seal and pull out the sword.
And she conflicts with the power of the Moon Sword.
Then the mysterious light in her body...
That's right.
It's the divine spirit of God of the Sun.
So,
I'm protecting the inheritor of God of the Sun?
But do you know who you are?
Why did you see the Battle of Two Gods in the illusion
as if it is your own experience?
Lu Li.
Because the half of the heart in your body
belongs to God of the Moonlight.
And God of the Moonlight and God of the Sun
are destined enemies.
You only have half a heart
because God of the Sun
split God of the Moonlight's heart into half.
Half of it is suppressed under the Four Seasons Monument.
Half of it turned into you.
You and Liu Shao inherited the hatred of the two gods.
That's why your spiritual power will oppose each other
and hurt each other.
If you lack the other half of heart,
you can only be the shadow of God of the Moonlight in mortal world.
You will disappear one day.
I want you to live
and God of the Moonlight to come back.
That's why I asked you to get the Moon Sword.
Only by using the Moon Sword
to break the Four Seasons Monument,
can you get back
the other half of your heart under the monument
and become God of the Moonlight completely.
Master,
did you already know that
if I become God of the Moonlight,
Liu Shao will die.
So what?
As long as you can become God of the Moonlight,
nothing else matters.
I'll give you one last chance.
Get back the Moon Sword from Liu Shao.
Otherwise,
there is nothing you can do but die.
Lu Li!
Liu Shao.
It's me.
You mustn't use your vitality anymore.
Here.
You just woke up.
Your spiritual power is injured
and you are still quite weak.
You have to eat something no matter what.
Thank you, He Na.
Sorry to bother you again
this time.
I'm happy that you asked me for help
at the most difficult time.
The Moon Sword!
Don't worry.
The Moon Sword is here too.
It's just that it's oppositing the spiritual power in your body.
To prevent you from being devoured,
I used water energy to cast a protection spell on the sword.
It is safe for now.
He Na.
Tell me.
What is his heart made of?
He can pretend to like you
so much that he may die for you.
I never doubted him.
But in the end,
I'm less important than a sword.
If she dies because of me,
I will not live selfishly.
If Master wants to sacrifice an innocent person,
why don't you start with me?
As long as Liu Shao can survive,
God of the Moonlight
has nothing to do with me.
So,
you broke up because of the Moon Sword?
What about you?
You also think all his kindness is fake.
All the things are just a lie.
Since you can't answer,
why don't you find an answer yourself?
Where can I find the answer?
Your heart.
You want to save Liu Shao with your life?
Fine.
Give me back half of your heart first.
There has always been a legend in the demon world.
On the full moon night,
the flute of the Melody Flute
can illuminate a bridge of heart.
As long as you think of the person you want to see the most,
you can walk on the bridge,
walk into the heart,
and find out the answer you want.
Liu Shao.
This is for you.
What are you waiting for?
Take it.
You must keep
the gift I gave you.
What you see and hear in the bridge of heart
is also what you think in your heart.
Silly girl,
you're so easily fooled.
No matter how precious you are,
there's no way you can compare with the Moon Sword.
That's the reflection of your heart.
Do you really want to die for her?
Lu Li, we're done.
Liu Shao.
I'm fine.
I am thinking that
he once swore with his life
to protect me
and save me.
What is his true heart?
What can I believe?
This half of heart that you value so much
is full of Liu Shao.
Maybe
he was sincere at that time.
No one can control himself while in love.
He can't be fake at most of the time.
I'm fine.
If he's heartless,
I will give him up.
There's nothing to worry about.
I just need time
to take a break.
I can make it.
Liu Shao.
If I miss you,
I'll regret it for the rest of my life.
Then don't miss me.
You did so much
just to save Liu Shao.
I can't do anything to the injury
caused by the devouring of the Moon Sword.
However,
I heard that the Bone-Corroding Harp of Immortal Ze Shui from the demon world
has strong healing power.
It might help her.
Master...
Rumor has it that the Bone-Corroding Harp has turned into a demon due to hatred
and is very vicious.
You might die
during the trip.
Master.
I once swore
I will love her and protect her forever
and never regret.
Even if I die,
I must save her.
Master,
remember to take your medicine on time.
Take care.
Your Majesty.
I'm fine.
But it is not a long-term solution
to treat Miss Liu with the water energy.
Besides, it's very harmful to you.
You can't use it anymore.
If we still have the Bone-Corroding Harp,
we can save Liu Shao.
If we can find the Bone-Corroding Harp...
It won't work.
It is hid in the wasteland
and full of hatred towards our clan.
If you go to find it,
you will be burned to death.
He Na!
Lu Li.
How's Liu Shao doing?
She was hurt both physically and mentally.
How can she be doing well?
It was my fault.
You have nothing to explain?
It was all my fault.
There's nothing to explain.
You didn't betray her
nor want to hurt her.
I tried to stop her from pulling out the sword,
but it was too late.
Something else happened after that.
That made her misunderstand.
Do you want to see her?
Of course.
But
if I go to see her now,
I will only bring her trouble.
I can't control
her injury caused by the devouring.
In a few days,
she may pass away.
So I need to find the Bone-Corroding Harp as soon as possible.
How do you know the Bone-Corroding Harp?
You really deserve your reputation as
the General of the Aquatic Demons.
Fu,
I don't deserve
such a big gift.
You are the famous Mr. Lu Sheng
who once worked with God of the Moonlight.
If I don't bring some gifts at our first meeting,
it may seem that I look down on you
Cut the crap.
Although we are different,
we have the same goal.
I want the Moon Sword.
Can you get it?
As long as you can find the person who broke the Four Seasons Monument,
I'm willing to do it.
I've already found the person.
Good.
Wait for my good news.
The Bone-Corroding Harp
is the magic weapon that Immortal Ze Shui once used.
It can calm one's mind
and heal one's physical and mental trauma.
It can even repair magic weapons.
So where is the Bone-Corroding Harp?
I heard it's in the wasteland.
But for thousands of years,
the world has changed.
The demon world moved mountains to fill the sea.
Ordinary people can't find it.
Then how can we find it?
The Aquatic Demons can feel the Bone-Corroding Harp.
But
we've been cursed by Immortal Ze Shui for generations.
As long as we get close to the Bone-Corroding Harp,
our body will split
and die because of the curse.
What if
I have a way to break the curse?
What is it?
Give me some water energy of the Aquatic Demons.
I can use the pain to feel the direction
and find the harp.
Do you know how painful it is
when your skin splits inch by inch?
He Na.
Don't waste time.
She can't wait.
Liu Shao.
Wait for me.
I will find it.
Liu Shao.
Wait for me.
I wonder what would my brother look like
if I strangle you to death?
When I find the Moon Sword,
I won't keep you alive.
Fu,
you are doing useless things again.
Since young,
you've put your most important things here.
Even the protection spell is the same.
No one can touch it,
except you.
Since you already knew,
why did you try again and again?
Because I overestimated myself.
I thought maybe in your heart,
I am different.
The Moon Sword
is not something we should touch.
It's not something we can touch?
Then who does it belong to?
Immortal Palace? Marquis Wuyang's Mansion?
Or Liu Shao who is lying inside?
I once thought since she could pull out the Moon Sword,
she should be capable.
But now she's dying.
Other than causing you more troubles,
what else can she do?
Get out.
You kicked me out for a woman?
What?
How could your demon energy be injured?
What happened?
Fu,
you are not allowed
to touch Liu Shao and the Moon Sword.
This is the energy-mixing pill we got
after we obtained the spirit fire.
Maybe it can help her regain some magic power
to resist the injury caused by the devouring.
You're injured too.
And this trip is full of danger.
This energy-mixing pill
might be more useful to you.
I am tough.
I may not need these at all.
Give this to her.
In the future,
please take care of her.
Lu Li.
You must come back alive.
I will.
I know someone is waiting for me.
I hope this pill from Lu Li
can give you some more time.
[Ice Rock Lake]
The water energy is working.
The more painful I am,
the closer I get to the Bone-Corroding Harp.
You accepted my water energy.
From now on,
every time you get one inch closer to the Bone-Corroding Harp,
your vitality will be weakened a little.
If you want to get the Bone-Corroding Harp,
you need to be prepared to risk your life.
You're awake.
Did I fall asleep for a long time again?
Not long.
You're lying again.
Every time you lie,
you don't talk much,
never wasting a word.
And you also lean to the left like this.
You can be seen through easily.
I'll write it down.
When it comes to lying,
you should learn from Lu Li.
Be confident
and be convincing.
Once,
Lu Li and I...
It's great that I can wake up.
When I fell asleep,
I thought I wouldn't wake up.
Liu Shao.
If you fall asleep again,
you have to remind yourself
that you must wake up.
There is someone who cherishes you,
loves you,
and values your life
more than his.
Do you mean my parents?
There is someone else.
Do you mean you?
Although you are my demon,
but I can't afford
such a powerful demon
like you, the Demon King.
How about me setting you free?
I mean...
Lu Li.
Don't mention him.
I should still have several days left.
Let me
feel the world
wholeheartedly.
Actually, you could woke up
because Lu Li gave you a pill.
It was given by Marquis Wuyang
after you obtained the spirit fire.
It's hot.
Show me your hands.
Look how badly you are injured.
He was injured at that time.
And he is going to a place
that may kill him.
He's going to get the Bone-Corroding Harp.
That harp
should be able to save you.
Save me?
The Bone-Corroding Harp hates the Aquatic Demons the most
so Lu Li asked me for some of my water energy.
He relies on the pain he feels when getting close to the harp
to determine the location.
The pain he's suffering now
is a thousand times more than mine.
I'm not sure if he can get the Bone-Corroding Harp.
I'm not even sure
if he can survive
when he reaches the Bone-Corroding Harp.
When he came to me,
he only cared about you.
As for the Moon Sword,
he never mentioned it.
Can you send me to him?
Lu Li has my water energy on him.
With it as the introduction
and the power of the Brahma tree as the guide,
I can send you to him immediately.
But if your injury relapses there,
no one can save you.
Even if I die,
I must go.
I want to ask him again.
Is the Moon Sword more important
or me?
Since you've made up your mind,
I can't stop you.
But promise me,
you and Lu Li
must come back alive.
The Bone-Corroding Harp.
Looks like Liu Shao was wrong.
If you only want to use Liu Shao,
why would you risk your life to go to the wasteland?
But you have to be careful of your Soul-Devouring Spell.
If you want to save Liu Shao, you must come back alive.
I can't die yet.
Liu Shao.
Liu Shao is waiting for me.
I won't let you die.
I won't.
Prove it to me.
Prove it?
Okay.
I will save you.
I can't give up.
I will get the Bone-Corroding Harp.
Get the Bone-Corroding Harp
and save...
Save Liu Shao.
Lu Li.
Liu Shao?
Is that you?
Is it really you?
Am I dreaming?
I have a lot to tell you.
I stopped you from pulling out the Moon Sword
because I didn't want you to get hurt because of it.
If I'm gone,
you must forget me.
Liu Shao.
I like you.
Lu Li.
Look carefully if this is a dream.
Liu Shao.
Why are you here?
Because I have a question for you.
But just now,
you have answered it.
Do you believe me?
I do.
Lu Li.
Even if I don't believe in my eyes and ears,
I will believe you.
No matter what happens in the future,
let's face it together.
OK.
The Bone-Corroding Harp...
What is it saying to me?
It said it hates...
Liu Shao!
Protection spell?
What's going on?
Liu Shao!
The man outside
has betrayed you.
But you
still have hope for him.
Remember,
all men in this world
are liars.
Look.
He wants to keep lying to you.
Look at that traitor's face.
Kill him.
Kill him!
Liu Shao.
Don't listen to his sweet words.
He just wants to use you.
Kill him!
Liu Shao.
Liu Shao!
Don't hesitate.
Do it!
Liu Shao!
The liar deserves to die!
Kill him!
Liu Shao!
Lu Li!
One more time.
You can injure him badly.
No.
Let him pay the price.
Let him experience the feeling of dying.
I believe Lu Li.
He has never betrayed me.
Even if I don't believe in my eyes and ears,
I will believe him.
You are just the resentment left in the harp
by Immortal Ze Shui.
No, you can't be trusted.
I have my own choice.
Liu Shao.
Lu Li.
Are you okay?
I got the Bone-Corroding Harp.
I saw it.
The spiritual power left by Immortal Ze Shui has disappeared.
It can't hurt the Aquatic Demons
or me.
But its healing power should still be there.
Just now,
I think I saw Immortal Ze Shui.
I gave the harp to her.
No.
It wasn't me.
Liu Shao.
You're too tired.
You still have the injury casued by the devouring.
Now,
you have to go back for treatment.
It's too dangerous here.
We were separated by the protection spell just now
so I couldn't protect you.
You can't get hurt again.
That voice
was full of hatred.
I don't want that to happen.
I don't want anything magnificent.
I just want to live with you forever.
But I'm afraid
I can't be with you forever.
When the curse mark return to your palm,
♫On rainy days, wind blows smoke♫
you will die for sure
♫Into circles♫
♫On both sides, I’m chanting♫
Even for one day.
♫The night is sleepless♫
♫The shadows of the moon are incomplete, and people are in love♫
Okay.
♫A cocoon of shadows♫
Let's be an ordinary couple
♫Your promise, my fate♫
who live an ordinary and happy life.
♫In spring, seasons changed♫
Liu Shao.
♫But my heart is still the same♫
Can you hold on?
♫Back to the sky, the clouds passing by♫
Of course I can.
♫Is like the things we went through♫
Let's find He Na
to fix the Bone-Corroding Harp first.
♫Beside the lake, on the boat♫
♫The moment we passed each other♫
♫Can compare with the rest of my life♫
♫I look at my love and send it to the clouds outside the garden♫
♫Looking at your ageless face at the end of the world♫
♫You put the winter snow in your ears and can’t hear it♫
♫When the flowers stop falling, you and I will miss each other♫
♫Everything in the world passes before understanding♫
[The Song of the Moon]